Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪I drift across the boundless skies♪
♪أتجول عبر السماء اللامحدودة♪
♪Through deserts where no one goes♪
♪عبر الصحاري حيث لا أحد يذهب♪
♪Seeking myself♪
♪أبحث عن نفسي♪
♪The self I long to find♪
♪الذات التي أتوق للعثور عليها♪
♪Lost in a maze of lies♪
♪ضائع في متاهة من الأكاذيب♪
♪I break into your sea of clouds♪
♪أقتحم بحرك من السحب♪
♪It traps me♪
♪إنه يحاصرني♪
♪It redeems me♪
♪إنه يخلصني♪
♪Which hue of the sky is your love?♪
♪ما هو لون السماء الذي يحبك؟♪
♪Or is it the burning flame♪
♪ أم أنها الشعلة المشتعلة ♪
♪Found only in storms?♪
♪توجد فقط في العواصف؟♪
♪You are the mark engraved upon my heart♪
♪أنت العلامة المحفورة على قلبي♪
♪From then on all my memories tremble for you♪
♪ومنذ ذلك الحين، كل ذكرياتي ترتجف من أجلك♪
♪What I cannot forget is that fleeting gaze♪
♪ما لا أستطيع أن أنساه هو تلك النظرة العابرة♪
♪What I cannot escape is passion born in chaos♪
♪ما لا أستطيع الهروب منه هو العاطفة المولودة في الفوضى♪
♪How I long to hold you again♪
♪كم أتوق إلى احتضانك مرة أخرى♪
♪Our love, high among the clouds♪
♪حبنا، عالياً بين السحاب♪
♪Is sealed with that kiss♪
♪مختوم بتلك القبلة♪
[Love in The Clouds]
[الحب في السحاب]
[Adapted from Bai Lu Cheng Shuang's "Love in The Clouds"]
[مقتبس من رواية "الحب في السحاب" لباي لو تشنغ شوانغ]
[Episode 30]
[الحلقة 30]
Spiritual power from Zhushui Spiritual State?
القوة الروحية من حالة تشوشوي الروحية؟
Did the Emperor of Zhushui give it to you?
هل أعطاك إياه إمبراطور تشوشوي؟
No wonder your power surged at the tea gathering.
لا عجب أن قوتك زادت في تجمع الشاي.
Who are you taking me to?
إلى من تأخذني؟
The Emperor of Zhushui?
امبراطور تشوشوي؟
So you were faking it all along!
إذن كنت تتظاهر بذلك طوال الوقت!
The black lingzhi mushroom can revive your cat.
يمكن لفطر لينجزي الأسود أن ينعش قطتك.
I'm sure Ming Xin knows that already.
أنا متأكد من أن مينغ شين يعرف ذلك بالفعل.
Do you intend to play along?
هل تنوي اللعب معنا؟
Is there anything else
هل هناك أي شيء آخر
in my mind that you can't read?
في ذهني أنك لا تستطيع القراءة؟
Right, Warrior Goddess.
يمينًا، إلهة المحاربة.
Everything is within your calculations.
كل شيء ضمن حساباتك.
Ming Xin will show himself.
مينغ شين سوف يظهر نفسه.
I want to settle the score with him
أريد أن أصفّي الحساب معه
and might as well use the opportunity
وقد يكون من الأفضل استغلال الفرصة
to get the last piece of the Recording Mirror.
للحصول على القطعة الأخيرة من مرآة التسجيل.
Do you dare return to Yaoguang Mountain?
هل تجرؤ على العودة إلى جبل ياوجوانج؟
What if Father punishes you?
ماذا لو عاقبك الأب؟
Punish me?
عاقبني؟
Why should I be afraid of that?
لماذا يجب أن أخاف من ذلك؟
When I reveal the truth to everyone,
عندما أكشف الحقيقة للجميع،
who should be afraid? You or me?
من يجب أن يخاف؟ أنت أم أنا؟
Now that you've fallen for the trap
الآن بعد أن وقعت في الفخ
let's settle our score once and for all.
دعونا نحسم أمرنا مرة واحدة وإلى الأبد.
Open your eyes and see
افتح عينيك وانظر
what I have here.
ما لدي هنا.
How can this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
Mu Qibai has half of the Recording Mirror.
لدى مو تشيباي نصف مرآة التسجيل.
How did you get the one in my possession
كيف حصلت على ما في حوزتي؟
that went missing?
التي اختفت؟
Impossible.
مستحيل.
You have the Heavenly Grief.
لديك الحزن السماوي.
How can you...
كيف يمكنك...
The Recording Mirror
مرآة التسجيل
will prove that you poisoned me with the Heavenly Grief
سأثبت أنك سممتني بالحزن السماوي
and colluded with the Emperor of Zhushui.
وتواطأ مع إمبراطور تشوشوي.
How do you think Yaoguang Palace will punish you?
كيف تعتقد أن قصر ياوجوانج سوف يعاقبك؟
Your punishment will be more important
عقوبتك ستكون أكثر أهمية
than my identity.
من هويتي.
I hate
انا اكره
that I didn't kill you back then in Jixing Abyss when I had
أنني لم أقتلك حينها في هاوية جيشينغ عندما كنت
the Blood Moon Ring that could catalyze the netherbeasts!
خاتم القمر الدموي الذي يمكن أن يحفز الوحوش السفلية!
Do you have any idea what you did?
هل لديك أي فكرة عما فعلته؟
You poisoned me so that you can be the crown prince.
لقد سممتني حتى تصبح ولي العهد.
That's a personal agenda.
هذه أجندة شخصية.
But letting the netherbeasts out
لكن السماح للوحوش السفلية بالخروج
will only bring suffering to the Six Realms!
لن يؤدي إلا إلى جلب المعاناة إلى العوالم الستة!
You're the greatest fool ever!
أنت أعظم أحمق على الإطلاق!
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Ming Xian.
مينغ شيان.
Were you the one
هل كنت أنت؟
who sealed the netherbeast army
من ختم جيش الوحوش السفلية؟
alongside Ji Bozai?
جنبًا إلى جنب مع جي بوزاي؟
Ji Bozai and you fell in love?
جي بوزاي ووقعت في الحب؟
How preposterous.
كم هو سخيف.
You ruined the plan of the Emperor of Zhushui.
لقد دمرت خطة إمبراطور تشوشوي.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
he will let you go?
هل سيسمح لك بالذهاب؟
Your right hand is your dominant hand.
يدك اليمنى هي يدك المسيطرة.
Therefore,
لذلك،
you poisoned me with your right hand.
لقد سممتني بيدك اليمنى.
Ming Xian, what are you doing?
مينغ شيان، ماذا تفعل؟
No!
لا!
Ming Xin.
مينغ شين.
You poisoned me.
لقد سممتني.
Because of that, my spiritual veins were damaged and I lost
وبسبب ذلك تضررت أوردتي الروحية وخسرت
in the tournament.
في البطولة.
To fulfill your selfish desire,
لتحقيق رغبتك الأنانية،
you forsook your duty to Yaoguang Mountain
لقد تخليت عن واجبك تجاه جبل ياوجوانج
and colluded with Zhushui Spiritual State.
وتواطأ مع الدولة الروحية تشوشوي.
You summoned the blood moon
لقد استدعيت القمر الدموي
and attempted to destroy Jixing Abyss with netherbeasts.
وحاول تدمير هاوية جيكسينج باستخدام الوحوش السفلية.
Today,
اليوم،
I shall take away all your dexterity.
سوف آخذ منك كل براعتك.
An eye
عين
for an eye.
للعين.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Mu Qibai told me
قال لي مو تشيباي
that only the Golden Millet Dream could cure the Heavenly Grief.
أن حلم الدخن الذهبي وحده قادر على علاج الحزن السماوي.
You can use your spiritual veins at will now,
يمكنك استخدام عروقك الروحية الآن كما تشاء،
which means you are cured.
وهذا يعني أنك قد شفيت.
Did Ji Bozai truly have the Golden Millet Dream
هل كان لدى جي بوزاي حقًا حلم الدخن الذهبي؟
and give it to you?
وأعطيها لك؟
[Diwu Tree Root]
[زيت جذر الشجرة]
My Lord.
سيدي.
Considering the two hundred or so
بالنظر إلى مائتي أو نحو ذلك
wandering spirits given by Yaoguang Mountain recently,
الأرواح المتجولة التي قدمها جبل ياوجوانج مؤخرًا،
you will soon master
سوف تتقن قريبا
the secret technique of Zhushui,
التقنية السرية لـ Zhushui
the art of illusory assassination.
فن الاغتيال الوهمي
Fuyue,
فويوي،
I once told you many times
لقد قلت لك مرارا وتكرارا
that I would never become like my father or brothers.
أنني لن أصبح مثل أبي أو إخوتي أبدًا.
You then asked
ثم سألت
if it was a promise to you
لو كان وعدا لك
or to myself.
أو لنفسي.
But I have seen the truth now.
ولكنني رأيت الحقيقة الآن.
The blood of Zhushui flows within us.
دم تشوشوي يتدفق في داخلنا.
Are we all that different?
هل نحن مختلفون إلى هذا الحد؟
We all worship the deities of Zhushui Spiritual State.
نحن جميعًا نعبد آلهة الحالة الروحية تشوشوي.
Perhaps we were all cursed from the start.
ربما كنا جميعا ملعونين منذ البداية.
Only by sacrificing our souls
فقط بالتضحية بأرواحنا
can we attain true heights.
هل يمكننا أن نصل إلى إرتفاعات حقيقية؟
If that is the price
إذا كان هذا هو الثمن
to rise above all,
للارتقاء فوق كل شيء،
so be it.
فليكن.
My Lord.
سيدي.
Whatever you have become,
مهما أصبحت،
you are still you.
أنت لا تزال أنت.
I will always stay by your side.
سأبقى بجانبك دائمًا.
I couldn't defeat her
لم أستطع هزيمتها
and she even broke one of my arms.
وحتى أنها كسرت أحد ذراعي.
My bone won't ever heal again.
عظمي لن يشفى مرة أخرى أبدًا.
The Recording Mirror...
مرآة التسجيل...
Wait.
انتظر.
I must talk to Father before she does.
يجب أن أتحدث مع والدي قبل أن تفعل ذلك.
The tea gathering isn't over.
لم ينتهي اجتماع الشاي بعد.
Why are you back so soon?
لماذا عدت سريعا؟
Father, I rushed back
أبي، لقد هرعت للخلف
because there's something affecting the name of Yaoguang Mountain
لأن هناك شيئًا يؤثر على اسم جبل ياوجوانج
that you must know.
هذا ما يجب عليك معرفته.
Whatever
أيا كان
could tarnish our reputation?
هل يمكن أن يشوه سمعتنا؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
All of you are dismissed.
لقد تم طردكم جميعا.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم جلالتك.
What happened to your arm?
ماذا حدث لذراعك؟
I met Ming Xian during the tea gathering.
التقيت مينغ شيان أثناء حفل الشاي.
He broke my arm.
لقد كسر ذراعي.
Ming Xian?
مينغ شيان؟
He's still alive?
هل مازال على قيد الحياة؟
Not only is he alive,
ليس فقط أنه على قيد الحياة،
but he also betrayed Yaoguang Mountain,
ولكنه خان أيضًا جبل ياوجوانج،
and sided with Jixing Abyss.
وانحاز إلى جانب جيكسينج أبيس.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Absolutely.
قطعاً.
I speak the truth.
انا اتكلم الحقيقة.
Moreover,
علاوة على ذلك،
I found something even more terrifying.
لقد وجدت شيئا أكثر رعبا.
Ming Xian
مينغ شيان
is a girl.
هي فتاة.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
I could hardly believe it at first
لم أستطع أن أصدق ذلك في البداية
because it was just ridiculous.
لأنه كان سخيفًا تمامًا.
But I saw it with my own eyes.
ولكنني رأيته بأم عيني.
The warriors with me can attest to it too.
ويمكن للمحاربين معي أن يشهدوا على ذلك أيضًا.
Ming Xian is a girl.
مينغ شيان هي فتاة.
She got a new name, Ming Yi,
حصلت على اسم جديد، مينغ يي،
and married Ji Bozai.
وتزوجت بوعز.
The so-called respected Empress must have told this lie
لا بد أن الإمبراطورة المحترمة المزعومة قد قالت هذه الكذبة
to secure her position.
لتأمين مكانتها.
She told everyone she had given birth to a son.
لقد أخبرت الجميع أنها أنجبت ابنًا.
Then, she had her daughter disguised as a man
ثم قامت بتمويه ابنتها في زي رجل
and deceived Yaoguang Mountain for 21 years.
وخدع جبل ياوجوانج لمدة 21 عامًا.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
He is my son.
إنه ابني
He is not a girl.
إنه ليس فتاة.
I do not know
لا أعلم
what evil trick the Empress used.
ما هي الخدعة الشريرة التي استخدمتها الإمبراطورة؟
But Ming Xian worked with the rival realm
لكن مينغ شيان عمل مع المملكة المنافسة
and lost on purpose during the Qingyun Tournament.
وخسرت عمدا خلال بطولة تشينغيون.
We then became one of the lower realms.
ثم أصبحنا من العوالم الدنيا.
This is the truth.
هذه هي الحقيقة.
I see.
أرى.
I shall investigate thoroughly.
سأقوم بالتحقيق جيدا.
If Jing Shu truly committed such an atrocity,
إذا ارتكب جينغ شو مثل هذه الفظاعة حقًا،
I would revoke her title as the Empress.
سأسحب منها لقب الإمبراطورة.
I have one more favor to ask.
عندي طلب آخر أريد أن أطلبه.
Father, after the tea gathering,
أبي، بعد حفل الشاي،
please hold the Crown Prince Conferment Ceremony
يرجى إقامة حفل منح وسام ولي العهد
and appoint me as the crown prince.
وعينوني وليا للعهد.
His Majesty said yes?
قال جلالته نعم؟
The conferment ceremony will be held after three days.
سيتم عقد حفل التكريم بعد ثلاثة أيام.
Then,
ثم،
I'll be the official crown prince of Yaoguang Mountain.
سأكون ولي العهد الرسمي لجبل ياوجوانج.
Great.
عظيم.
Great!
عظيم!
Xin.
اطلب.
Why do you look so worried?
لماذا تبدو قلقا هكذا؟
Mother.
الأم.
There's one more problem.
هناك مشكلة اخرى.
I procured the Heavenly Grief from Mu Qibai.
لقد حصلت على الحزن السماوي من مو تشيباي.
He recorded everything with the Recording Mirror.
لقد سجل كل شيء باستخدام مرآة التسجيل.
And the mirror
والمرآة
is in Ming Xian's possession.
توجد في حوزة مينغ شيان.
What?
ماذا؟
Then...
ثم...
Then you should get the mirror back from her.
يجب عليك إذن استعادة المرآة منها.
But Ming Xian somehow got back her spiritual veins.
لكن مينغ شيان استعادت بطريقة ما عروقها الروحية.
She's too strong for me.
إنها قوية جدًا بالنسبة لي.
But the Emperor of Zhushui
لكن إمبراطور تشوشوي
suspects Ming Xian of being the descendant of the Bo clan.
يشتبه في أن مينغ شيان هو من نسل عشيرة بو.
He asked me to capture her alive and bring her to Zhushui Spiritual State.
لقد طلب مني أن ألتقطها حية وأحضرها إلى الحالة الروحية تشوشوي.
Assuming he is right,
على افتراض أنه على حق،
then Ming Yi
ثم مينغ يي
does not carry the bloodline of Yaoguang Palace.
لا يحمل سلالة قصر ياوجوانج.
[Bo's Medical Classics]
[كلاسيكيات بو الطبية]
Spiritual veins destroyed by the Heavenly Grief
الأوردة الروحية المدمرة بالحزن السماوي
may only be restored by planting the Golden Millet Dream in the victim.
لا يمكن استعادتها إلا عن طريق زراعة حلم الدخن الذهبي في الضحية.
There is no other alternative.
لا يوجد بديل آخر.
The Heavenly Grief in me suddenly went away.
لقد اختفى الحزن السماوي بداخلي فجأة.
The only possible explanation
التفسير الوحيد الممكن
is that you gave it to me.
هل هذا هو ما أعطيته لي؟
But I had no idea at all.
ولكن لم يكن لدي أي فكرة على الإطلاق.
It seems like you have dealt with Ming Xin swiftly.
يبدو أنك تعاملت مع مينغ شين بسرعة.
It is unscathed.
إنه لم يصب بأذى.
To revive your companion beast,
لإحياء رفيقك الوحش،
you need to resonate with it using your spiritual veins.
أنت بحاجة إلى التفاعل معه باستخدام عروقك الروحية.
It will be painful.
سيكون مؤلمًا.
Let me stay here with you.
دعني أبقى هنا معك.
The black lingzhi mushroom is working.
فطر لينجزي الأسود يعمل.
If I nurture it for a while,
إذا قمت برعايته لفترة من الوقت،
Twenty-Seven will return.
سوف يعود سبعة وعشرون.
I finally did it.
لقد فعلتها أخيرا.
What?
ماذا؟
Won't you ask
هل ستسأل؟
what I did to Ming Xin?
ماذا فعلت مع مينغ شين؟
After all, he was going to be
بعد كل شيء، كان سيكون
the crown prince of Yaoguang Mountain.
ولي عهد جبل ياوجوانج.
If I hurt him,
إذا أذيته،
Jixing Abyss might be in trouble.
قد يكون Jixing Abyss في ورطة.
In trouble?
في ورطة؟
As in neither of us
كما هو الحال في أي منا
can handle the consequences?
هل تستطيع تحمل العواقب؟
If you kill him, I'll bring you the blade.
إذا قتلته، سأحضر لك النصل.
If you spare him, I'll cover your tracks.
إذا تركته، سأقوم بتغطية آثارك.
I have the Warrior Goddess with me.
لدي إلهة المحاربة معي.
What else is there to worry about?
ما الذي يدعو للقلق أيضًا؟
I got the Recording Mirror,
لقد حصلت على مرآة التسجيل،
but I spared Ming Xin.
لكنني أنقذت مينغ شين.
He's going to reveal my identity to my father.
إنه سيكشف هويتي لأبي.
And you
وأنت
already have a plan?
هل لديك خطة بالفعل؟
Yes.
نعم.
But
لكن
there's one important thing
هناك شيء واحد مهم
I need to check with you.
أريد التحقق معك.
When did you give me the Golden Millet Dream?
متى أعطيتني حلم الدخن الذهبي؟
♪Maybe I'm just your firefly♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد يراعة لك♪
♪That's why I'm so fragile...♪
♪لهذا السبب أنا هش للغاية...♪
Didn't you see me
ألم تراني
destroy the Golden Millet Dream?
تدمير حلم الدخن الذهبي؟
How could I possibly give it to you?
كيف يمكنني أن أعطيك إياه؟
I undid the seal on Bo's Medical Classics.
لقد قمت بفك الختم على كلاسيكيات بو الطبية.
The Golden Millet Dream
حلم الدخن الذهبي
is the only cure for the Heavenly Grief.
هو العلاج الوحيد للحزن السماوي.
You gave it to me.
لقد أعطيته لي.
Like I said,
كما قلت،
I did not.
لم أفعل.
In Zhangwei Mountain, you asked if I was Ming Xian.
في جبل تشانغوي، سألتني إذا كنت مينغ شيان.
You said you'd only ask me that question one last time.
قلت أنك ستسألني هذا السؤال للمرة الأخيرة فقط.
So today,
لذلك اليوم،
I'm asking you again one last time.
أسألك مرة أخرى للمرة الأخيرة.
If you won't answer my question,
إذا لم تجيب على سؤالي،
I will not ask it again.
لن أسأله مرة أخرى.
♪My faint light♪
♪ضوئي الخافت♪
♪Will shine through for your brilliance♪
♪سوف تتألق من خلال تألقك♪
♪If your world was once an endless wasteland♪
♪إذا كان عالمك ذات يوم أرضًا قاحلة لا نهاية لها♪
♪I'd tear myself apart to fill the wounds inside you♪
♪سأمزق نفسي لملء الجروح بداخلك♪
♪Even if this life is like a shooting star♪
♪حتى لو كانت هذه الحياة مثل نجم ساقط♪
♪Brief only for the sake of meeting you...♪
♪مختصر فقط من أجل مقابلتك...♪
Did you enjoy the scallion pancake?
هل استمتعت بفطيرة البصل الأخضر؟
You brought a scallion pancake to Zhangwei Mountain?
هل أحضرت فطيرة البصل الأخضر إلى جبل تشانغوي؟
Is it weird?
هل هذا غريب؟
I came here for you anyway.
لقد أتيت هنا من أجلك على أية حال.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
I only realized now
لقد أدركت ذلك الآن فقط
that you're more important to me
أنك أكثر أهمية بالنسبة لي
than I imagined.
مما كنت أتخيل.
Don't spill anything.
لا تسكب أي شيء.
Come. Eat it.
تعال، كل ذلك.
♪The fireflies fill the night sky...♪
♪تملأ اليراعات سماء الليل...♪
See?
يرى؟
I'd hate to see you
لا أريد رؤيتك
look at me like that.
انظر إلي هكذا.
I gave you the Golden Millet Dream
لقد أعطيتك حلم الدخن الذهبي
for one purpose only,
لغرض واحد فقط،
so that you can live.
لكي تتمكن من العيش.
I don't want you to feel indebted to me
لا أريدك أن تشعر بالدين لي
or that you need to do anything to repay me.
أو أنك بحاجة إلى القيام بأي شيء لسداد لي.
♪Even in this restless world♪
♪حتى في هذا العالم المضطرب♪
♪My faint light♪
♪ضوئي الخافت♪
♪Will shine through for your brilliance♪
♪سوف تتألق من خلال تألقك♪
♪If your world was once an endless wasteland...♪
♪إذا كان عالمك ذات يوم أرضًا قاحلة لا نهاية لها...♪
You ought to know me better.
ينبغي عليك أن تعرفني بشكل أفضل.
I'm a prideful woman.
أنا امرأة فخورة.
I will never fall for someone out of indebtedness.
لن أقع في حب شخص بسبب الديون أبدًا.
Yes. You and your pride.
نعم. أنت وكبريائك.
You're invincible.
أنت لا تقهر.
♪In this fleeting life♪
♪في هذه الحياة العابرة♪
♪I'll still be your light♪
♪سأظل نورك♪
Ji Bozai.
جي بوزاي.
Ming Xian.
مينغ شيان.
You two trespassed into Yaoguang Palace
لقد دخلتما إلى قصر ياوجوانج
to kidnap me.
لخطفني.
What?
ماذا؟
Are you betraying Yaoguang Mountain
هل تخون جبل Yaoguang
and siding with Jixing Abyss now?
والوقوف إلى جانب Jixing Abyss الآن؟
Looking for something?
هل تبحث عن شيء ما؟
Oh, this thing from the Emperor
أوه، هذا الشيء من الإمبراطور
of Zhushui?
من Zhushui؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Easy.
سهل.
It won't be for long.
لن يستمر ذلك طويلاً.
I can finally
أستطيع أخيرا
use this Soul-seizing Technique on you.
استخدم تقنية الاستيلاء على الروح هذه عليك.
Are you ready?
هل انت مستعد؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
The Emperor of Zhushui gave you power
لقد أعطاك إمبراطور تشوشوي القوة
and even the compass.
وحتى البوصلة.
What did he tell you to do?
ماذا قال لك أن تفعل؟
Ming Xian.
مينغ شيان.
Do you think you can be the crown prince
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع أن تكون ولي العهد؟
just because you have the Recording Mirror?
فقط لأن لديك مرآة التسجيل؟
Dream on!
إحلم!
You will not steal my thunder again!
لن تسرق رعدي مرة أخرى!
Ming Xian.
مينغ شيان.
Only I can be the crown prince.
أنا فقط من يستطيع أن يكون ولي العهد.
So his greatest fear
لذلك فإن أعظم مخاوفه
is you?
هل انت؟
That's my loser of a brother for you.
هذا هو الخاسر من أخي بالنسبة لك.
Don't mind him.
لا تهتم به.
Smiling? You have no right to be smug.
مبتسم؟ ليس من حقك أن تكون مغرورًا.
What did the Emperor tell me to do?
ماذا قال لي الإمبراطور أن أفعل؟
Listen carefully.
استمع بعناية.
He told me to capture you alive and bring you to Zhushui Spiritual State.
لقد طلب مني أن ألتقطك حيًا وأحضرك إلى الحالة الروحية تشوشوي.
You're an outsider.
أنت شخص غريب.
You don't carry
انت لا تحمل
the bloodline of Yaoguang Palace.
سلالة قصر ياوجوانج.
You
أنت
are a descendant of the Bo clan!
هو من نسل عشيرة بو!
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
The elders in Yaoguang Palace claimed
وادعى كبار السن في قصر ياوجوانج
that two wandering physicians once sojourned in Yaoguang Mountain.
أن طبيبين متجولين كانا يقيمان ذات مرة في جبل ياوجوانج.
One of them
واحد منهم
fell in love and had a child with one of the local warriors.
وقعت في الحب وأنجبت طفلاً من أحد المحاربين المحليين.
Can you guess
هل يمكنك التخمين؟
if it's you?
إذا كنت أنت؟
The Emperor of Zhushui also said
وقال إمبراطور تشوشوي أيضًا
that since you could enter the Zhulong Barrier,
بما أنك تستطيع الدخول إلى حاجز تشولونغ،
it meant you were the descendant of the Bo clan.
وهذا يعني أنك من نسل عشيرة بو.
Father. Mother.
الأب. الأم.
Look.
ينظر.
The crown prince of Yaoguang Mountain can only be me!
ولي العهد لجبل ياوجوانج لا يمكن أن يكون إلا أنا!
Let me find out the truth in Yaoguang Palace.
دعني أكتشف الحقيقة في قصر ياوجوانج.
Ming Yi.
مينغ يي.
Father has found out.
لقد اكتشف الأب ذلك.
He has erected a barrier
لقد أقام حاجزا
so that I cannot return.
حتى لا أتمكن من العودة.
The barrier is now broken.
لقد تم كسر الحاجز الآن.
Guards will arrive soon.
الحراس سوف يصلون قريبا.
Don't worry. I'll stand guard.
لا تقلق، سأقف حارسًا.
No one will bother you.
لن يزعجك أحد.
Ming Yi.
مينغ يي.
I can handle it.
انا قادر على التعامل مع هذا الأمر.
You...
أنت...
How did you come back?
كيف عدت؟
How could they do this to you?
كيف يمكنهم أن يفعلوا بك هذا؟
They know you're a fairy.
إنهم يعرفون أنك جنية.
So they agreed to appoint Ming Xin as the crown prince.
لذلك اتفقوا على تعيين مينغ شين وليا للعهد.
You shouldn't have come back.
لم يكن ينبغي عليك العودة.
I'll take you away from this place.
سأأخذك بعيدا عن هذا المكان.
Your father thinks you're a traitor.
والدك يعتقد أنك خائن.
Even you can't be sure that you can get out of this place
حتى أنك لا تستطيع أن تكون متأكداً من أنك تستطيع الخروج من هذا المكان
alive.
على قيد الحياة.
And you want me to come with you?
وتريدني أن آتي معك؟
Do you think you can escape?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع الهروب؟
Master told me
قال لي المعلم
that you were safe in Yaoguang Palace.
أنك كنت بأمان في قصر ياوجوانج.
Look at you now.
أنظر إليك الآن.
I will bring you to safety even if it means
سأوصلك إلى بر الأمان حتى لو كان ذلك يعني
everyone will view me as an enemy.
الجميع سوف ينظرون إلي كعدو.
Just go.
فقط اذهب.
I will not leave with you.
لن أتركك .
Your Majesty, you won't come with me
جلالتك لن تأتي معي
because you don't think I can bring you to safety
لأنك لا تعتقد أنني أستطيع أن أوصلك إلى بر الأمان
or because
أو لأن
I am not your daughter?
أنا لست ابنتك؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Ming Xin was given the task of taking me back alive
لقد تم تكليف مينغ شين بمهمة إعادتي حيًا
by the Emperor of Zhushui
من قبل إمبراطور تشوشوي
because the Emperor found out
لأن الإمبراطور اكتشف ذلك
that I do not carry the bloodline of Yaoguang Palace.
أنني لا أحمل سلالة قصر ياوجوانج.
He said I was a descendant of the Bo clan.
قال أنني من نسل عشيرة بو.
No wonder you never called me Mother
لا عجب أنك لم تناديني بأمي أبدًا
after you barged into this place.
بعد أن اقتحمت هذا المكان.
Master She.
سيدتي هي.
Ming Yi wrote to me,
كتب لي مينغ يي،
telling me that you gave the Golden Millet Dream to her.
أخبرتني أنك أعطيتها حلم الدخن الذهبي.
I've never thanked anyone in my life.
لم أشكر أحدًا قط في حياتي.
But I'll make an exception today.
ولكنني سأصنع استثناءً اليوم.
Stand upright.
قف بشكل مستقيم.
Master She.
سيدتي هي.
Do not return the bow.
لا تعيد القوس.
Rest assured.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.
I will repay the favor.
سأرد الجميل.
I will find the Diwu tree's core as soon as possible
سأجد قلب شجرة الديوو في أقرب وقت ممكن
and make the Golden Millet Dream for you.
وأصنع لك حلم الدخن الذهبي.
Thank you, Master She.
شكرا لك يا سيدتي شي.
No need.
لا حاجة.
Ming Yi also mentioned
وذكر مينغ يي أيضًا
that Ming Xin accused her of being a descendant
أن مينغ شين اتهمها بأنها من نسل
of the Bo clan.
من عشيرة بو.
Did that happen?
هل حدث ذلك؟
What else did Ming Xin say?
ماذا قال مينغ شين أيضًا؟
Tell us.
أخبرنا.
So where did the wandering Bo physicians go?
فأين ذهب أطباء بو المتجولون؟
I was told one died from labor complications.
أخبروني أن أحدهم مات بسبب مضاعفات الولادة.
And the other one was last seen
والاخر شوهد اخر مرة
leaving Yaoguang Palace
مغادرة قصر ياوجوانج
with a newborn baby.
مع طفل حديث الولادة.
You returned
لقد عدت
to find the truth.
للعثور على الحقيقة.
If I tell you the truth,
إذا قلت لك الحقيقة،
will you stop pestering me?
هل ستتوقف عن مضايقتي؟
Have you ever wondered
هل تساءلت يوما
why I have treated you so
لماذا عاملتك هكذا
ever since you were little?
منذ أن كنت صغيرا؟
You are smart.
أنت ذكي.
You won every Qingyun Tournament.
لقد فزت بكل بطولة Qingyun.
You wouldn't even dare
لن تجرؤ حتى
to make a mistake or lose
ارتكاب خطأ أو الخسارة
in your training.
في تدريبك.
But I never cared
ولكنني لم أهتم أبدا
what you wanted,
ما أردته
or if you were hurt
أو إذا كنت قد تعرضت للأذى
or hungry.
أو جائعا.
No mother would ever
لن تفعل أي أم ذلك أبدًا
treat her child like this.
تعامل طفلها بهذه الطريقة.
Given your intelligence,
نظرا لذكائك،
I thought you'd have guessed it.
اعتقدت أنك قد خمنت ذلك.
So...
لذا...
So who am I?
فمن أنا؟
Your father, the Emperor of Yaoguang,
والدك، إمبراطور ياوجوانج،
and I do not love each other.
وأنا لا أحب بعضنا البعض.
He took Madam Meng in as his consort one day
لقد اتخذ السيدة منغ زوجة له ​​في أحد الأيام
and showered her with affection.
وأمطرها بالمودة.
Everyone in Yaoguang Palace said
قال الجميع في قصر ياوجوانج
that when Madam Meng gave birth
أنه عندما أنجبت السيدة منغ
to a son with spiritual veins,
إلى ابن ذو عروق روحية،
she would replace me
انها سوف تحل محل لي
as the Empress of Yaoguang.
كإمبراطورة ياوجوانج.
Therefore,
لذلك،
I must give birth to a son
يجب أن أنجب ابنا
with spiritual veins before she does.
مع الأوردة الروحية قبل أن تفعل ذلك.
[20 Years Ago]
[منذ 20 عامًا]
There, there.
هناك، هناك.
Good boy.
ولد جيد.
Baby. My baby.
حبيبتي. حبيبتي.
Quick.
سريع.
Bring me my baby.
أحضر لي طفلي.
My baby.
طفلي.
Impossible. This can't be right.
مستحيل. هذا لا يمكن أن يكون صحيحًا.
My son must have spiritual veins.
لا بد أن يكون لدى ابني عروق روحية.
- Who would have thought - Impossible!
- من كان يظن - مستحيل!
This is impossible!
هذا مستحيل!
The son whom I toiled so much to conceive
الابن الذي تعبت كثيرا من أجل إنجابه
was born without spiritual veins?
وُلِد بدون أوردة روحية؟
Without spiritual veins?
بدون عروق روحية؟
Yes. The irony of it.
نعم، يا لها من سخرية.
God took pity on me and gave me a son.
لقد رحمني الله وأعطاني ابنًا.
But in everyone's eyes,
ولكن في عيون الجميع،
he's just a useless person with no spiritual veins.
إنه مجرد شخص عديم الفائدة وليس لديه أي عروق روحية.
He can never be a crown prince.
لن يتمكن أبدًا من أن يصبح وليًا للعهد.
He won't even be able to survive.
لن يكون قادرًا حتى على البقاء على قيد الحياة.
So
لذا
who am I?
من انا؟
The serendipitous but hapless victim
الضحية السعيدة ولكن التعيسة
of this tragedy.
من هذه المأساة.
Coincidentally,
بالمصادفة،
another baby was born
وُلِد طفل آخر
at the same time in Yaoguang Palace.
في نفس الوقت في قصر ياوجوانج.
It was a baby girl
لقد كانت طفلة
yet she was born with strong spiritual veins.
ولكنها ولدت بأوردة روحية قوية.
So I made the decision.
لذلك اتخذت القرار.
To save my son,
لإنقاذ ابني،
I took you, who were born on the same day, away
لقد أخذتك، أنت الذي ولدت في نفس اليوم، بعيدًا
to replace my son.
ليحل محل ابني.
Your Majesty, I'm begging you.
جلالتك، أنا أتوسل إليك.
Yucen is already dead.
يوسن مات بالفعل.
This is her only child.
وهذا طفلها الوحيد.
Bo Yulan, you know very well
بو يولان، أنت تعرف جيدًا
why your sister died from birth complications.
لماذا ماتت أختك بسبب مضاعفات الولادة؟
She was hunted down by Zhushui Spiritual State
لقد تم مطاردة من قبل تشوشوي الدولة الروحية
and was gravely injured.
وأصيب بجروح خطيرة.
She was too weak to carry a baby,
لقد كانت ضعيفة جدًا بحيث لا تستطيع حمل طفل،
yet she risked everything to deliver her baby
ولكنها خاطرت بكل شيء لتلد طفلها
for the sake of love.
من أجل الحب.
And her lover
وحبيبها
couldn't do anything to protect her baby.
لم تتمكن من فعل أي شيء لحماية طفلها.
He is a warrior
إنه محارب
but he consummated with a foreign fairy.
ولكنه استكمل علاقته بجنية أجنبية.
He is now imprisoned.
وهو الآن مسجون.
I felt bad for Yucen,
لقد شعرت بالأسف تجاه يوسن،
so I snuck her into the palace for her delivery.
لذا قمت بإدخالها خلسةً إلى القصر لتسليمها.
Now that Yucen is gone,
الآن بعد أن رحل يوسين،
do you think you can protect the baby?
هل تعتقد أنك تستطيع حماية الطفل؟
This baby was born with unrivaled
وُلِد هذا الطفل بميزات لا مثيل لها
spiritual veins and potentials.
الأوردة والإمكانات الروحية.
She is destined to rise above all.
إنها مقدر لها أن ترتفع فوق كل شيء.
I know
أنا أعرف
your clan has something called the Veil of Illusion
عشيرتك لديها شيء يسمى حجاب الوهم
that can conceal her gender.
التي يمكنها إخفاء جنسها.
You and your sister
أنت وأختك
used that technique to evade the manhunt
استخدم هذه التقنية للتهرب من المطاردة
in Zhushui Spiritual State.
في حالة Zhushui الروحية.
Tell me how to use the technique
أخبرني كيف أستخدم هذه التقنية
and I'll release your sister's lover.
وسأطلق سراح حبيب أختك.
This baby
هذا الطفل
will be the respected crown prince of Yaoguang Mountain.
سيكون ولي العهد المحترم لجبل ياوجوانج.
I will make her the ruler of Six Realms.
سأجعلها حاكمة للعوالم الستة.
So,
لذا،
I really am...
انا حقا...
Yes, the daughter of Bo Yucen,
نعم ابنة بو يوسين
the descendant of the Bo clan.
سليل عشيرة بو.
Then, my father is...?
ثم والدي هو...؟
Master She.
سيدتي هي.
I heard
لقد سمعت
that the ancestors of the Bo clan would leave behind portraits.
أن أسلاف عشيرة بو سيتركون وراءهم صورًا.
As long as someone pays respect to the portraits,
طالما أن هناك من يحترم الصور،
their divine consciousness
وعيهم الإلهي
will remain in the Bo clan's ancestral home.
سوف تبقى في موطن عائلة بو.
That day, in Zhangwei Mountain,
في ذلك اليوم، في جبل تشانغوي،
Ming Yi
مينغ يي
saw another fairy from the Bo clan,
رأيت جنية أخرى من عشيرة بو،
Bo Yucen.
بو يوسين.
She saw Yucen?
هل رأت يوسن؟
She truly saw Yucen?
هل رأت يوسين حقًا؟
So, you do know Bo Yucen.
إذن، أنت تعرف بو يوسين.
Fairy Bo Yucen
الجنية بو يوسين
said something weird to Ming Yi.
قال شيئا غريبا لمينغ يي.
What did she say?
ماذا قالت؟
The Bo clan still has one descendant in this world.
لا يزال لعشيرة بو نسل واحد في هذا العالم.
And that's my child.
وهذا طفلي.
But I hope
ولكنني آمل
no one will ever find out
لن يكتشف أحد ذلك أبدًا
about her identity
عن هويتها
or whereabouts.
أو مكان وجوده.
Oh, my baby.
أوه، طفلي.
Never have I ever imagined
لم اتخيل ذلك ابدا
that I would be able to see you again.
أن أتمكن من رؤيتك مرة أخرى.
Ming Yi
مينغ يي
didn't know what she meant.
لم أعرف ماذا تعني.
But...
لكن...
Master She, you must know.
سيدتي، يجب أن تعرفي.
I thought
اعتقدت
that if Ming Yi could meet her,
إذا استطاع مينغ يي مقابلتها،
it means someone is still paying respect to her portrait.
وهذا يعني أن شخصًا ما لا يزال يحترم صورتها.
Is that you, Master She?
هل هذا أنت يا سيدتي؟
Master She,
سيدتي هي
I admit
انا اعترف
that I once asked my companion beast to dig around your past.
أنني طلبت ذات مرة من رفيقي الوحشي أن يحفر حول ماضيك.
Ming Xian became a warrior of Yaoguang Mountain at the age of 13.
أصبح مينغ شيان محاربًا في جبل ياوجوانج في سن الثالثة عشر.
And you
وأنت
suddenly did everything you could
فجأة فعلت كل ما بوسعي
to be the venerable for Yaoguang Mountain's warrior ranks.
أن تكون موقرًا لصفوف المحاربين في جبل ياوجوانج.
That's because
هذا بسبب
you want to tutor the crown prince, Ming Xian.
تريد أن تقوم بتدريس ولي العهد، مينغ شيان.
Well done!
أحسنت!
Greetings, Venerable.
تحياتي سيدي الموقر.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
No need to bow to me, Venerable.
لا داعي للانحناء لي، يا سيدي الموقر.
I am now one of the warriors.
أنا الآن واحد من المحاربين.
I should bow to you instead.
ينبغي لي أن أنحني لك بدلا من ذلك.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
your form was excellent just now.
لقد كان شكلك ممتازًا للتو.
Perhaps you shouldn't call me Venerable.
ربما لا ينبغي لك أن تناديني بالمبجل.
Let me be your master.
دعني أكون سيدك.
I'll take you in as my disciple.
سأعتبرك تلميذي.
You?
أنت؟
Why should I be your disciple?
لماذا يجب أن أكون تلميذك؟
What can you teach me?
ماذا يمكنك أن تعلميني؟
Prideful, aren't you?
أنت فخور، أليس كذلك؟
Let's have a match then.
دعونا نلعب مباراة إذن.
If I win,
إذا فزت،
you'll have to call me Master.
سيتعين عليك أن تناديني بالسيد.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
After Ming Xin
بعد مينغ شين
confessed,
اعترف
you began to suspect me, didn't you?
لقد بدأت تشك بي، أليس كذلك؟
I didn't mean to offend you.
لم أقصد الإساءة إليك.
All I'm after is the truth.
كل ما أريده هو الحقيقة.
Will you tell me the truth, Master She?
هل ستخبرني الحقيقة يا سيدتي؟
Were you in love
هل كنت في الحب؟
with Fairy Bo Yucen?
مع الجنية بو يوسين؟
Your father
والدك
was the warrior
كان المحارب
of Yaoguang Mountain, She Tianlin.
جبل Yaoguang، شي تيانلين.
So in the Bo clan's ancestral home, I met
لذا في منزل عائلة بو، التقيت
my mother.
والدتي.
The one I've known since I was little,
الذي أعرفه منذ أن كنت صغيرًا،
the one who has been staying by my side,
الشخص الذي ظل بجانبي
the one whom I call Master is...
والذي أسميه سيد هو...
So Ming Yi
لذلك مينغ يي
is your child with Fairy Bo Yucen.
هل طفلك مع Fairy Bo Yucen؟
When Yucen went into labor,
عندما دخلت يوسين في المخاض،
I was imprisoned by the Empress.
لقد تم سجني من قبل الإمبراطورة.
When I was released,
عندما تم إطلاق سراحي،
Yucen had already passed
لقد مر يوسين بالفعل
from birth complications.
من مضاعفات الولادة.
I couldn't even look at her one last time.
لم أستطع حتى النظر إليها للمرة الأخيرة.
By then,
بحلول ذلك الوقت،
your daughter
ابنتك
had already become the son of the Empress.
لقد أصبح بالفعل ابن الإمبراطورة.
I was at my wits' end.
لقد وصلت إلى نهاية ذكائي.
I had no other option.
لم يكن لدي خيار آخر.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
I was just an ordinary warrior
لقد كنت مجرد محارب عادي
and they were the entire Yaoguang Palace.
وكانوا قصر ياوجوانج بأكمله.
Could I fight them all?
هل يمكنني محاربتهم جميعا؟
Could I fight the Empress?
هل أستطيع محاربة الإمبراطورة؟
I could only endure it silently.
لم أستطع أن أتحمل ذلك إلا بصمت.
Yucen's portrait
صورة يوسين
contains our shared memories.
يحتوي على ذكرياتنا المشتركة.
For 21 years,
لمدة 21 عاما،
for all 21 years,
طوال الـ 21 سنة،
those cherished past memories,
تلك الذكريات الماضية العزيزة،
and Ming Yi's future
ومستقبل مينغ يي
have kept me alive.
لقد أبقوني على قيد الحياة.
For 21 years,
لمدة 21 عاما،
have you never intended
هل لم تقصد ذلك مطلقا؟
to tell Ming Yi the truth?
لأخبر مينغ يي الحقيقة؟
You would rather Ming Yi live
كنت تفضل أن يعيش مينغ يي
in deception forever?
في الخداع إلى الأبد؟
♪When the drifting clouds♪
♪عندما تتحرك السحب♪
♪Flow toward me♪
♪تدفق نحوي♪
♪They drench my very soul♪
♪إنهم يغرقون روحي♪
♪Until it turns weak♪
♪حتى يصبح ضعيفًا♪
♪I deceive myself into thinking that to love once♪
♪أخدع نفسي بالاعتقاد بأن الحب مرة واحدة♪
♪Is enough♪
♪يكفي♪
♪Even if no true vow has ever been given♪
♪حتى لو لم يتم تقديم أي نذر حقيقي على الإطلاق♪
♪From the stars, how long must my tears travel to reach your heart?♪
♪من النجوم، كم من الوقت يجب أن تسافر دموعي لتصل إلى قلبك؟♪
♪The tenderness you give me is but love's poisonous wine♪
♪الحنان الذي تمنحني إياه ليس إلا نبيذ الحب السام♪
♪I drink down all of my sorrow♪
♪أشرب كل حزني♪
♪To trade for your freedom♪
♪للتجارة من أجل حريتك♪
♪Once I've tasted love, I long to be lost in its wine♪
♪بمجرد أن ذاقت الحب، أتوق إلى الضياع في نبيذه♪
♪After long struggles in the abyss, I ask the heavens♪
♪بعد صراع طويل في الهاوية، أطلب من السماء♪
♪Even if my armor shatters for you, what does it matter?♪
♪حتى لو تحطم درعي من أجلك، فما الذي يهم؟♪
♪Fate is never wrong♪
♪القدر لا يخطئ أبدًا♪
♪Even the sun must one day fall♪
♪حتى الشمس يجب أن تغرب يومًا ما♪
♪Against the world's absurdity, I fight with all my might♪
♪أحارب بكل قوتي ضد عبث العالم♪
♪From the stars, how long must my tears travel to reach your heart?♪
♪من النجوم، كم من الوقت يجب أن تسافر دموعي لتصل إلى قلبك؟♪
♪The tenderness you give me is but love's poisonous wine♪
♪الحنان الذي تمنحني إياه ليس إلا نبيذ الحب السام♪
♪I drink down all of my sorrow♪
♪أشرب كل حزني♪
♪To trade for your freedom♪
♪للتجارة من أجل حريتك♪
♪Once I've tasted love, I long to be lost in its wine♪
♪بمجرد أن ذاقت الحب، أتوق إلى الضياع في نبيذه♪